<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<!--
  ~ Copyright (C) 2016 The Android Open Source Project
  ~
  ~ Licensed under the Apache License, Version 2.0 (the "License");
  ~ you may not use this file except in compliance with the License.
  ~ You may obtain a copy of the License at
  ~
  ~      http://www.apache.org/licenses/LICENSE-2.0
  ~
  ~ Unless required by applicable law or agreed to in writing, software
  ~ distributed under the License is distributed on an "AS IS" BASIS,
  ~ WITHOUT WARRANTIES OR CONDITIONS OF ANY KIND, either express or implied.
  ~ See the License for the specific language governing permissions and
  ~ limitations under the License.
  -->
<resources>
    <string-array name="games">
        <item>Counter Strike</item>
        <item>Paladins</item>
        <item>Limbo</item>
        <item>Dead by Deadlight</item>
        <item>Evolve</item>
        <item>Broforce</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="game_desc">
        <item>Counter-Strike (officially abbreviated as CS) is a series of multiplayer first-person shooter video games, in which teams of terrorists and counter-terrorists battle.
        </item>
        <item>Paladins is a First Person Shooter game developed by Hi-Rez Studios</item>
        <item>Limbo is a puzzle-platform video game developed by independent studio Playdead.</item>
        <item>Dead by Daylight is an asymmetric survival horror video game</item>
        <item>Evolve is a first-person shooter video game developed by Turtle Rock Studios, published by 2K Games and distributed by Take-Two Interactive.</item>
        <item>Broforce is a side-scrolling run-and-gun platform video game developed by Free Lives and published by Devolver Digital.</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="game_details">
        <item>The game was followed-up with Counter-Strike: Condition Zero, developed by Turtle Rock Studios and released in 2004.
            Later that same year, Counter-Strike: Source was released by Valve. Released only eight months after
            Counter-Strike: Condition Zero, in November 2004, the game was a remake of the original Counter-Strike and the first
            in the series to run on Valves newly created Source engine.
        </item>
        <item>Each player controls a champion character with differing abilities, and they are split into two teams who compete
            to achieve objectives. In response to accusations that the game is an Overwatch clone, Hi-Rez COO Todd Harris said that
            "Overwatch was not the inspiration for Paladins", and "the game that deserves the most credit is Team Fortress 2".
        </item>
        <item>Limbo is a 2D sidescroller, incorporating the physics system Box2D to govern environmental objects and the player
            character. The player guides an unnamed boy through dangerous environments and traps as he searches for his sister.
            The developer built the games puzzles expecting the player to fail before finding the correct solution. Playdead
            called the style of play "trial and death", and used gruesome imagery for the boys deaths to steer the player from
            unworkable solutions.
        </item>
        <item>A group of survivors – anywhere from one to four players (typically four) – must elude one player who is the killer
            in an enclosed area at night which will either be a secluded forest, an abandoned junkyard, a decrepit cornfield, a
            haunted asylum, a dark swamp or the small town of Haddonfield, Illinois. The survivors perspectives are third-person,
            while the killers perspective is first-person.
        </item>
        <item>Evolve is an action video game with a focus on both co-operative, and competitive, multiplayer gameplay. The game
            adapts a 4v1 asymmetrical structure where four players take control of the Hunters, while the fifth player controls
            the Monster. The Hunters main objective is to track and hunt the Monster in a limited amount of time, while the
            Monsters goal is to evolve and make themselves more powerful.</item>
        <item>The player-character is a bro, a hypermasculine action hero-style commando, who fights terrorists and rescues his bro
            teammates and prisoners of war from captivity. The games destructible environments wear away with the players
            gunfire. The levels end when the player defeats a devil boss, hoists an American flag, and leaves via helicopter
            while the scenery explodes.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <array name="game_avatar">
        <item>@drawable/a_avator</item>
        <item>@drawable/b_avator</item>
        <item>@drawable/c_avator</item>
        <item>@drawable/d_avator</item>
        <item>@drawable/e_avator</item>
        <item>@drawable/f_avator</item>
    </array>
    <array name="games_picture">
        <item>@drawable/a</item>
        <item>@drawable/b</item>
        <item>@drawable/c</item>
        <item>@drawable/d</item>
        <item>@drawable/e</item>
        <item>@drawable/f</item>
    </array>
</resources>
